let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "For more diversity, the level of disturbance should be",
        answer: "intermediate",
        options: [
          "less",
          "intermediate",
          "more",
          "none of these"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Hierarchy emerges almost inevitably through a wide variety of evolutionary processes, for the simple reason that hierarchical structures are _____ (fill in the blank)",
        answer: "stable",
        options: [
          "perfect",
          "imperfect",
          "stable",
          "unstable"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "\"Groups of actually or potentially interbreeding natural populations which are reproductively isolated from other such groups\" is a definition of",
        answer: "species",
        options: [
          "cells",
          "species",
          "ecosystems",
          "biomes"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The emergent principle can be stated as",
        answer: "whole > sum of parts",
        options: [
          "whole = sum of parts",
          "whole < sum of parts",
          "whole > sum of parts",
          "none of these"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "There is more biodiversity in areas with",
        answer: "more competition, more predation",
        options: [
          "less competition, less predation",
          "less competition, more predation",
          "more competition, more predation",
          "more competition, less predation"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The mitochondrion is a/an",
        answer: "sub-cellular organelle",
        options: [
          "sub-cellular organelle",
          "cell",
          "tissue",
          "organ"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "\"The diversity that exists among different geographies\" is",
        answer: "gamma biodiversity",
        options: [
          "alpha biodiversity",
          "beta biodiversity",
          "gamma biodiversity",
          "delta biodiversity"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "\"The diversity that exists within an ecosystem\" is",
        answer: "alpha biodiversity",
        options: [
          "alpha biodiversity",
          "beta biodiversity",
          "gamma biodiversity",
          "delta biodiversity"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The hierarchical system was given by",
        answer: "Simon",
        options: [
          "Simon",
          "Watson",
          "Hutchinson",
          "Humboldt"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The laboratory approach to ecology uses",
        answer: "experiments",
        options: [
          "equation",
          "models",
          "observations",
          "experiments"
        ]
    }
]